

# DMITRII KOLCHIN

# Student | Part-time Developer

# CONTACT

- (980) 446-9750
  - awhlycommercial@gmail.com

  - Charlotte, North Carolina
- https://awhly.wtf

### CONTACT

#### Professional

- Communication
- Problem Solving
- Teamwork
- Flexibility
- Creativity

#### Techincal

- Foreign Language
- Data Analysis
- Web Design
- Customer Support

PROFILE \_\_\_\_

I'm an enthusiastic student who is 20 years old, from Russia with a diverse range of interests, including data science, computer programming, filmmaking, photography, and language in general. I put initiative through volunteer work and I have a commitment to academic excellence, recognized with a "Certificate of Recognition in Advanced English 4". I will say that it is pretty easy for me at collaborating within teams and eager to contribute a unique perspective.

EDUCATION

2012-2022

Elementary School - High School

Russia, Moscow, School No.1530

GPA: 3.4

2022-2024

High School

NC, Charlotte, Myers Park HS

EXPERIENCE \_\_\_\_\_

# Sorter/Packager

Loaves & Fishes (May 2024 - September 2024)

- Helped food bank operations by receiving, sorting, and organizing donated food items. This involved categorizing donations by type (e.g., canned goods, produce, grains, baked goods, etc.).
- Assembled food packages for distribution, ensuring a balanced and varied selection of items based on general dietary needs.
- Contributed for over 14 volunteer hours to these activities, directly supporting the efficient flow of resources to individuals and families.



**INTERESTS** 

Photography

Programming

Travel

Gaming

EXPERIENCE	

# Hired Worker

Kolchin LLC (July 2024 - Present)

- Constructing custom cabinetry for kitchens, bathrooms, and other residential spaces.
- o Maintained a safe and organized work environment.

ACHIVEMENTS		_	

"C" programming cource

2018 - 2018

Finished basic "C" programming cource

Academic Excellence in English 4

2023-2024

Studied English 4 in Myers Park HS and was awarded an Academic Excellence for my achivements.